Hey, what's up everybody? It's Amanda Seals and I'm celebrating the incredible winners of the AT&T
Rising Future Makers Showcase. And this program empowers HBCU students to take their dreams to
new heights by connecting them with industry leaders and tools to support their endeavors.
I feel very strongly that education is the key to liberation and I'm proud to partner with an
initiative celebrating that. And so I want to say a big congratulations to Jordan Braithwaite,
an aspiring attorney in her fourth year at a Louisiana HBCU. Now Jordan is also the president
of an organization that advocates passionately for social justice and those impacted by the
criminal justice system. Jordan's on-campus work, leaning voter education and accessibility
initiatives has already reached hundreds of other students. Understanding of the law is always and
has always been foundational to the pursuit of equality for black folks in this country.
That knowledge is crucial, y'all. And honestly, it doesn't get talked about enough.
It's something I am personally just coming to truly understand. We learn about individuals
and we learn about movements, but it's so important for us to learn about the law when we are talking
about social justice in America. So I commend you again, Jordan, making that connection and fighting
that fight. And to all of you out there, make sure to check out the AT&T Dream in Black Microsite
to meet all 25 of this year's incredible winners from HBCU's Nationwide. Until next time, remember
to dream in black.